Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
- Series IV. Teaching, Research Materials and Lectures
  - FES- Islam in Indonesia, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - FES- Islam in Indonesia, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - FES- Geography of S.E.A. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - FES 202- Philippines (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - FES 202- Indonesia, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - FES 222- Islam (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Center for Strategic Studies- Washington D.C., May 1968 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous course materials (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Series V. Speeches and Meetings
  - Speech materials (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Speech materials (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Speech materials (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Chicago, June 3-5 1968 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Speech materials (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Speech materials (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Random materials (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, May 30, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Chicago, Nov. 30, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Rutgers, Apr. 18, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Singapore Conference-papers presented, July 1972 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Monash: Vietnam, Resida, Indonesia, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Cornell University (Bailey Hall), May 5, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Speeches (Cincinnati and Washington D.C.), May 4, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Speech (Smith College), Apr. 14, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Old Speeches (Washington D.C.) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Tokyo Conference, Sept. 4-7 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Tokyo materials (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - A Polarization of Knowledge, Aug. 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Conf. on Now Priorities (Washington D.C.), Oct. 8, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Smith College, Apr. 15, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pentagon Papers (Raleigh, N.C.), Jan. 18, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Indonesia Briefing (Washington D.C.), Jan. 23, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - SEADAG, Oct. 1-2 1974 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Japan, Nov-Dec 1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Cornell, Apr. 25, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - AAS, Nov. 18, 1972 & June 15, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - AAS (New Orleans and Brockport), 1972-73 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Cambodia Senate, Mar. 6, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - SEATO: Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Mar. 6, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Philippines (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - SEATO and U.S. Philippine and Geneva Documents (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Cornell, Oct. 6 & 15, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Cambodia: Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Leknas- Jakartz, May 6, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Washington-State Department Conference, Mar. 11, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - New Democratic Coalition, Jan. 7-8 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - MFP & Antioch Law- Washington D.C., Sept. 22, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Kyoto Conference, Nov-Dec 1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Columbia, Oct. 14, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Pendle Hill, Sept. 9-11 1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Washington Drafts, Mar. 28, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Washington, Mar. 27-29 1964 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Utah, May 9, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Cornell, Apr. 8, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Circle, Sept. 17, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Cornell, Apr.-May 1969 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Cornell, Spring 1969 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Cornell, Spring 1969 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Cornell (press releases), Spring 1969 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Cornell (press releases), Spring 1969 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Cortland, Apr. 29, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - University Kebangsaam, Dec. 1981 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - China & SEA-Steve Butler's Class, Apr. 15, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Hawaii, Feb. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Hawaii, Feb. 21-22, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Cornell-Faculty Vietnam Study Group (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Berrigan (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - AAS-Foreign Policy Committee (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - AAS-Foreign Policy Committee (continued) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bulletin of Atomic Scientists, June 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Moratorium Book (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Unpublished articles (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Abortive NYT article, Fall 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Senate materials and The New Republic Article, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The New Republic articles and miscellaneous materials, 1974-75 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - The Pentagon Papers: A critical evaluation, June 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Published articles and editorials (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Washington Star article and Kraft article, 1971-72 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Senator's Cambodia, May 14-15, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper articles (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Translations of articles in Bulletin of Atomic Scientists (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Printed articles (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Printed articles (continued) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica articles (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Nixon's Peace Plan- New Republic, Feb. 12, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Kennedy: Rob (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Sen. Hatfield materials (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Goodell materials (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Fulbright materials (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Memoranda (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Pentagon Papers: Ellsburg Trial (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Pentagon Papers (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Pentagon Papers (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Pentagon Papers: review (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Pentagon Papers (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Reviews (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Spiegel & Waltz (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - McGovern materials (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - McGovern materials (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - McGovern materials (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Senators (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Statement of the 26, Jan. 6, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Tuxedo, NY (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Romney materials (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - McGovern-Asia Panel, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Kahin and Popkun American Policy: Southeast Asia, June 1970 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Memo for McCarthy (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Senator McCarthy's Vietnam Advisory Group (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Senator McCarthy's Vietnam Advisory Group (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Senator McCarthy's Vietnam Advisory Group (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - McCarthy materials (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Additions
  - Paris, May 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Paris- G.M. Kahin, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - South Vietnam, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Elections, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Paris- G.M. Kahin, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - NLF- Seven Points, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - North Vietnam- Interviews, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Hanoi Negotiations, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Saigon Notes, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - North Vietnam Negotiations, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - The New Republic, Oct. 1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Prisoners of War (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - G.M. Kahin- U.S., 1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Paris- G.M. Kahin, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam Adresses (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - List of Intellectuals in Paris (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Paris- Adresses & Logistics (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - War and Crimes in Europe( Stockholm, Oslo, Paris)-I (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - War and Crimes in Europe( Stockholm, Oslo, Paris)-II (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Ellison- Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - WGBH-I (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - WGBH-II (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - J.Paul Vann, Spt 1965- August 1967 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Bundy on Elections (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - DeVillers for WGBH, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Takashi Oka- Letters (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Indo- China Communist Party, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - French Political Organization in Indo-China- D. Laguardia, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Roosevelt, Churchill & Indochina, 1942-45 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Extract from U.S. Senate: Causes, Origins & Legions of the Vietnam War, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Vietnam: French Period (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - U.S. Policy- Pre-Geneva, 1945-54 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - J.F.Kennedy, April 6th, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - B. Fall on Vietnam (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Sen. McCarthy's Speech (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - C.I.P- Commercial Import Program (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - DeViller's Lecture- Vietnam, 1954-60 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Articles on South Vietnam, 1960-63 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - White Paper, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - U.S. Overthrow of Diem (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Vietnam Press, Spring 1964 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Tonkin Gulf (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Coup Attempt- Gen Duc, Sept. 14, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - White Paper, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Legitimation of the Thieu Government (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - 1967 Elections- New 1980-81 Data (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Ellsberg on 1967 Elections (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Nixon's Presidency (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Fulro- The Thing Called Autonomy Movement, Sept. 1965 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - South Vietnam- Land Reform, 1966-69 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Statistics on Vietnamese Education, 1966-67 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The Saigon Regime- Constituent Assembly and Constitution (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Interviwes & Meetings, 1967-73 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - SVN- U.S. Role NYT, Khanh's Overthrow, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Prof. Cao Huy Thuan- Conversation, Oct. 1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Takashi Oka:Buddhism as a Political Force, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - South Vitenam- Ethnic Minorities (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Non-Communist Political Parties (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Tia Sang- Series on Events in Central Vietnam, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - The Saigon Regime- Press & Censorship (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - News Media- Vietnam (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - South Vietnam Refugees (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Political Prisoners, 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Tran Van Van- Assassination, Dec 1966 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Elections-I (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Elections-II (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Elections-III (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam Elections-I, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Vietnam Elections-II, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Tet. Offensive- Newsweek, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Khe Sanh (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Offensive, Feb. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Offensive, May, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - The Third Offensive (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Paris Digest- French Press, Jna- April 1968 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Pst Tet. Military (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Post Tet. Political (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - NSSM-1- Kissinger: Vietnam Options, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Hamlet Elections, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Vietnamisation (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Vietnam Situation, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Vietnam Situation- Clippings, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Vietnam Roundups- Arthur Dommen, July- Nov- 1970 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Vietnam Elections, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Vietnam Roundups- Arthur Dommen, Mar- April 1971 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Telephone Directories- Genral+ 3rd Corps, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - South Vietnam: Corrutption & Crime, 1971-74 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Issues in Vietnam's Presidential Elections, Oct 1971 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Vietnam- General, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Economic Conditions (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Spring Offensive- D. Elloitt, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Vietnam, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - South Vietnam- Internal, 1972-75 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Regugees, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam Clippings, 1973-78 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Third Force (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Alliance (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - NLF (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - The CRIMP Document (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Republic of Vietnam- Maps (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - NLF Origins (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - DNLFSV Politics, NLF Documents (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - NLF- Organization (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - NLF- External Relations (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - NLF, Aug. 1967 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - NLF- Sept 1970- July 1971, Analyzed & Compared (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - NLF- Negotiating Positions (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Provisional Revolutionary Government, Sept 1972, Mar. 1974 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - North Vietnam (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - North Vietnam- General, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Minorities- North Vietnam (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Hanoi- Leadership (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Working Paper on North Vietnamese Role on the war in South Vietnam (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Letter of LeDuan, Mar. 1966 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Gen. Vinh, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Dudman's Trip, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Salisburg & Schoenbrun- Report for Hanoi (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Letter of Nguyen Xuan (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Various Statements on the War & Negotiations- Hanoi (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Hanoi Negotiations, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Fullbright Memo, Aug 1971 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Hanoi Negotiating Position, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - North Vietnam: Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Letters, Correspondence, Booklists (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Media (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Negotiations, 1964-65 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Negotiations, 1965-66 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Negotiations- Chronological (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Bundy, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Bunker- Westmoreland Statements, Nov 1967 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Negotiations, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Policies- Administration (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1968 Negotiations Articles (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Bundy- East Asia Advisory Panel, April 1968 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Settlement Prospects & Proposals, 1967-68 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - "Understanding", 1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - South Vietnam Solution (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Paris Talks, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Negotiations, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Past Nixon Positions (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Nixon- Pre-Election (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Nixon- Speech, May 1969 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Nixon, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Negotiations, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Nixon, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - McGov. Amendment, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Nixon, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Nixon, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Negotiations- General, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Mc Govern Speech, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - New Phase Negotiations, Oct. 1972 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Draft Agreement, Oct. 1972 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Demands for Revision (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Peace Talks & South Vietnam, Dec. 1972 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Thieu on Negotiations (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Thieu's Interpretation - U.S. Entry and Communists Rights (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Post-War Economic Reconstruction (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Interpretation & Comment: Jan 1973 Accords (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Negotiations- Analysis (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - International Conferences & Joint Communique, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Nixon, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Accord, Jan 24, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - P.R.G. Reaction to Paris Accord (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Press Clippings on the U.S. Covert War in Indochina (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - U.S. Presence, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Violations of Jan 24 1973 Accords (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Political Prisoners-I (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Political Prisoners-II (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Implementation, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Air War (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Chemical War & Defoliants (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Thieu Regime & Economic Aid (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - China: Reaction to the U.S. Vietnam Policy (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Soviet & China Aid (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Russia & Vietnam (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - China & Vietnam (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Vietnam, China & Russia (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - America & The Vietnam War (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Hanoi's View of Thailand (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Japanese Opinions towards the Korean & Vietnam Wars (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Legislation to End the War, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - The War Powers Act, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Foreigh Aid Bill & Hearings, Feb 1973 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Coalition to Stop Funding the War (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Funding of the War (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam Normalization (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Post-War Reconstruction (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam Post-War, May 1975-78 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - U.N. Mission Report to North & South Vietnam, March 1976 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - G.Porter- Analyses, 1975-77 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Prisoners of War- Vietnam (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Southern Catholics on Negotiation, Jan 1968 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Third Force- Overseas Buddhist View (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Saigon- Thiev on Negotiations (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Vietnamese Buddhist Peace Delegation to Paris (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Vietnamese in France (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Coalition Government (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Buddhist Peace Delegation to Paris (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Neutralization (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Economic Impact of the Vietnam War on South-East Asia (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Survey of Vietnam Hamlets (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Military Situation - General (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - South Vietnam Pacification-I (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - South Vietnam Pacification-II (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Psychological War (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Congress & the War (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Congress Ad-hoc Committee, Jan 1966 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Zablocki Statements (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Policies- Congressional Record (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Propaganda (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Summary of Views on Vietnam War by Leading Presidential Candidates (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Humphrey Barnett (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - McCarthy (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Governor G. Romney (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - McGovern (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Senators' Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Policies- Other Policies- Opposition Senators (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Letter from Americans in Vietnam (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Amnesty (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Costs of Vietnam War- Leilenberg & Olson Draft (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Statistics on War (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Statistics on War- Comparison of U.S., Soviet & Chinese Support (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Vietnam: Laos: AAS: McAuliff (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Vietnam Studies Bulletin (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Vietnamese to be Interviewed in the U.S. (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Perspective on Vietnam, 1979-82 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Grenada & Salvador (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Salvador & Vietnam (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Reagan & Vietnam (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Vietnam, 1979-82 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Vietnam, Cambodia, China & U.S.S.R (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Indo-China, 1978-80 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Comments on Pacific Affairs Article, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Khan's Coup, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Overthorw of Minh, Jan 1964 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - The American Friends of Vietnam Program, April 1965 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Khan's Re-coup, Jan 1965 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Vietnam- I, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Vietnam- II, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Buddhist Crisis- Vetted Useful, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Formation of Ky Thien Government (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Rationale for Intervention (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - SINO Soviet Aid (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rocamora- Vietnam 1965; Sino- Soviet Context (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - China Factor, 1950-68 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Bombing Decision, 1964-65 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Bombing will Raise Morale and Strengthen Southern Base, April 1965 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Taylor Vs Khanh-Post Bundy Visit (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - G.V.N. Concurrence (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Tonkin (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Chrinological Developments, Aug 1964- Dec 1965 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Ecological Polarization, 1967-73 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Koreans in Vietnam (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Phillipines & Vietnam (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Phoenix (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Cambodia- A. Barnett (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Cambodia (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Myths & Illusions- Vietnam (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Thailand, 1979-81 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Vietnam Camdodia Relationship- Nayan Chanda (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Porter Gary- I.C. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Thailand, China, U.S., Cambodia, Vietnam (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - The Vietnam War- Introduction + Conclusion (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Limitations of the FOI Act (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Biographies (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Brig. Gen. Nguyen Chanh Thi (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Exodus- South, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - D.R.V. for U.S. Military Intervention (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Saigon Bound by France (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - The International Commission for Supervision & Control in Vietnam, May 1966 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Elections, 1954-56 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Catholics (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Geneva & its Implementation, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - 1955 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - U.S. Policy in the event of a Renewal of Agression in Vietnam, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Displacement of France, 1954-56 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - French Assembly Debates- Post Geneva (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Montgomery Papers (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - C.I.P. (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - U.S. Economic Policy- Godfrey E.J., 1954-60 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - The Ordeal of the South Vietnamese Industrial Sector- Wackernagel R. (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Economic & Technical Assistance Program for Vietnam International Co-operation Admin (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - The Anti-U.S. Resistance War for National Salvation, 1954-75 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - The Path of Revolution in the South (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - How Armed Struggle Began in South Vietnam (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - The CRIMP Document (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - The United StatesNgo Dinh Diem & the Rise of NLF, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Truong Nhu Tang- The Myth of a Liberation, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Vietnam- Documents & Research Notes (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Declaration of Former Resistance, March 1960 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - The Rebellion Against Diem Regime, 1957-58 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - 1963 Coup- Important Documents (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - NLF, 1963-64 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Pelz- Overthrow of Diem (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Coup Against Diem, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Removal of Diem, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Insurrection, 1957-59 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Attempted Coup of 1960 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Coup Against Diem- Pre-coup (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - U.S. Involvement in the Overthrow of Diem (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - The United Staes & the Fall of Diem- Geoffrey Warner (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - The Overthrow of Diem (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Rise of NLF (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - Vietnamese Reds Step up Killing, April 1960 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - Cleveland- U. Thant (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy's Public Relations Campaign, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Lodge (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Overthrow of Diem (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Various Coup Groups (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Assassination (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- Tran Van Don (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - The Coup of Jan 30, 1964- Tran Van Don (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Council for Foreign Relations Study Groups on Indi-China- Chapter I & II (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Bombing Rationale (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - North Vietnamese Troops to the South & Use of Bombing Rationale, 1964-66 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Chapter IV (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Chapter V- Decline of Diem (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Chapter VIII- Removal of Minh (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Khanh & NLF (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Removal of Khanh- Final Steps (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Coup against Khanh (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Buddhists, Neutralists & Pre-Negotiations (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Peace Movements, June 1965 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Sam Adams, Dec '66- April'68 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Ball- Notes & Memos (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Bill Bundy (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - William Bundy- Elections (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - William Bundy- Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - William Bundy- Oral History (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Diem- Musolf, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Ton That Dinh (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Tran Van Don-I (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Tran Van Don-II (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Anthony Eden (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Ellesberg- Memo, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Eisenhower (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Kennedy Documents, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - General Khanh (Box 34, Folder 34)